[{
    "prompt": "Which Star Wars movie was filmed entirely in the studio?",
    "answers": [
        "Attack of the Clones",
        "Return of the Jedi",
        "Star Wars",
        "Revenge of the Sith"
    ],
    "correct": "4"
},
{
    "prompt": "Which of the three main heroes (Luke, Leia, and Han Solo) in the first Star Wars trilogy refused to sign a three picture deal?",
    "answers": [
        "They all signed",
        "Harrison Ford",
        "Mark Hamill",
        "Carrie Fisher"
    ],
    "correct": "2"
},
{
    "prompt": "What color is Mace Windu's lightsaber",
    "answers": [
        "Purple",
        "Green",
        "Blue",
        "Red",
        "Yellow",
        "Orange"
    ],
    "correct": "1"
},
{
    "prompt": "Approximately how many languages can C-3PO speak?",
    "answers": [
        "6",
        "600",
        "6000",
        "6 billion",
        "6 million"
    ],
    "correct": "5"
},
{
    "prompt": "Is Jabba species a HUTT?",
    "answers": [
        "True",
        "False"
    ],
    "correct": "1"
},
{
    "prompt": "Who are the only two characters who appear in every Star Wars movie?",
    "answers": [
        "C-3PO and R2-D2",
        "Han and Chebacca",
        "Luke and leia",
        "Darth Vadar and Yoda"
    ],
    "correct": "1"
},
{
    "prompt": "What did Luke cut off the Wampa with his lightsaber?",
    "answers": [
        "Leg",
        "Head",
        "foot",
        "ear",
        "arm"
    ],
    "correct": "5"
},
{
    "prompt": "Was Yoda 700 years old when he died",
    "answers": [
        "True",
        "False"
    ],
    "correct": "2"
},
{
    "prompt": "Rogue One has an opening crawl â€“ true or false?",
    "answers": [
        "True",
        "False"
    ],
    "correct": "2"
},
{
    "prompt": "Who killed Qui-Gon Jinn?",
    "answers": [
        "Darth Bane",
        "Darth Vadar",
        "Darth Sidiuos",
        "Darth Maul"
    ],
    "correct": "4"
},
{
    "prompt": "Geroge Lucas Created Star Wars?",
    "answers": [
        "True",
        "False"
    ],
    "correct": "1"
},
{
	"prompt": "What, according to C-3PO, were the odds of successfully navigating an asteroid field?",
	"answers": [
		"4,890 to one",
		"8,970 to one",
		"3,720 to one",
		"725 to one"
	]
	"correct": "3"
},
{ 
     "prompt": "Above what planet does Cloud City hover?",
     "answers": [
         "Coruscant",
         "Mustafar",
         "Wobani",
         "Bespin"
     ]
     "correct": "4"
 },
 {
     "prompt": "What ship has no landing gear?",
     "answers" : [
         "Y-Wing",
         "YT-1300",
         "X-Wing",
         "TIE fighter"
     ]
     "correct": "4"
 },
 {
     "prompt": "What does TIE stand for?"
     "answers" : [
        "Twin Ion Engines",
        "Two Identical Engines",
        "Triangle Isometric Electrodes",
        "None of the above"
     ]
     "correct": "1"
 },
 {
     "prompt": "Who supplied the voice for Darth Vader?"
     "answers" : [
        "James Earl Jones",
        "Richard LeParmentier",
        "David Prowse",
        "Garrick Hagon"
     ]
     "correct": "1"
 },
 {
     "prompt": "Which actor played R2-D2?"
     "answers" : [
        "Jack Purvis",
        "Kenny Baker",
        "Anthony Daniels",
        "Peter Mayhew"
     ]
     "correct": "2"
 },
 {
     "prompt": "Who was Luke Skywalker's tail gunner in the Battle of Hoth?"
     "answers" : [
        "Wedge Antilles",
        "Dak Ralter",
        "Derek Klivian",
        "Wes Janson"
     ]
     "correct": "2"
 },
 {
     "prompt": "What is the name of the species that Yoda is the last member?"
     "answers" : [
        "Trilith",
        "Yolor",
        "Yangral",
        "Unknown"
     ]
     "correct ": "4"
 },
 {
     "prompt": "approximately how much time passed between Episode 4, A New Hope and Episode 5, The Empire Strikes Back?"
     "answers" : [
        "1 year",
        "2 years",
        "3 years",
        "6 months"
     ]
     "correct": "3"
 }]
